<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LNMIIT</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">Splash</string>
    <string name="weblink">lnmiit.ac.in</string>
    <string name="academics">Academics</string>
    <string name="admissions">Admissions</string>
    <string name="placements">Placements</string>
    <string name="administration">Administration</string>
    <string name="faculty">Faculty</string>
    <string name="student">Students</string>
    <string name="emergency">Emergency</string>
    <string name="bus">Bus</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="dining">Dining</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="about">About Us</string>

    <string name="intro_ug">The primary objectives of establishing the LNM INSTITUTE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY JAIPUR
        (LNM IIT Jaipur) are:-\n
•To create a platform, comparable to the best in the world,\n
•To become an effective catalyst for technological and societal development of the country,\n
•To provide the highest level of education in information technology,\n
•To produce competent, creative and imaginative engineers, in areas related to information technology,\n
•To promote the spirit of free and objective enquiry.\n

The Institute is currently running the following Four Year B.Tech Programmes:-</string>

    <string name="ug_cse">"The CSE discipline is supported by a team of faculty members having excellent research
        credentials as well as extensive industry experience. The lab facilities include Programming Lab, Digital
        Communication Lab, DBMS Lab, and Computer Networks Lab.The branch focusses on emerging trends like Software
        Engineering, Distributed and Cloud Computing, Data Mining, Data Warehousing and Multi-core Architecture."</string>

    <string name="ug_ece">The ECE team is a fine blend of renowned as well as young and dynamic faculty members,
        having education and experience from renowned institutions in India and abroad. Advanced courses and electives
        in later years enable students to specialise in communications, signal processing, robotics, VLSI, embedded
        systems, and other streams. The ECE department also offers specialized M.Tech. and Dual Degree programs
        inCommunication Systems, Microelectronics, Microwave engineering and VLSI.</string>

    <string name="ug_cce">The discipline is ably supported by an excellent team of faculty members, many of them having
        extensive industry-based experience in the fusion of software and hardware technologies. The CCE lab facilities
        include the Electronics Lab, Analog Communication Lab, Programming Lab, Digital Communication Lab, DBMS Lab, and
        Computer Networks Lab, ECAD Lab, and Microwave and Optical Communication Lab.</string>

    <string name="ug_mme">The MME discipline is supported by a team of faculty members having excellent research
        credentials as well as extensive industry experience.The branch helps students to deal with the real life
        challenges in the field of Mechanical and Mechatronics industries and equip them with the fundamental concepts
        and techniques of mechatronics applications, relevant to emerging technological advancements.It also focusses
        on Computer Aided Manufacturing, Design Engineering, Automation, Robotics.</string>

    <string name="intro_pg">The goals of the postgraduate programs at the LNM Institute of Information Technology (LNMIIT)
        Jaipur are: The development of scientific and engineering manpower of the highest quality, to cater to the needs of
        industry, R &amp; D organizations and educational institutions, a broad grasp of the fundamental principles of the
        sciences and scientific methods, a deep understanding of the area of specialization, an innovative ability to solve
        new problems, and a capacity to learn continually and interact with multidisciplinary groups. Above all, the students
        should have a capacity for free and objective inquiry, courage and integrity, awareness and sensitivity to the needs
        and aspirations of society. </string>

    <string name="mtech">•M. Tech Program students, irrespective of their discipline, must do a minimum of 28 credits through course work and a minimum of 36 credits through research (thesis) work.\n
•M. S. (by Research) Program students, irrespective of their discipline, must do a minimum of 16 credits through course work and a minimum of 48 credits through research (thesis) work.
        </string>

    <string name="abt_phd">
•With M. Tech degree, irrespective of their discipline, must do a minimum of 16 credits through course work and a minimum of 64 credits through research (thesis) work.\n
•With Msc, MA and M Phil degree, irrespective of their discipline, must do a minimum of 24 credits through course work and a minimum of 64 credits through research (thesis) work.\n
•With B. Tech degree, irrespective of their discipline, must do a minimum of 32 credits through course work and a minimum of 64 credits through research (thesis) work.
        </string>

    <string name="ug_me">The MME discipline is supported by a team of faculty members having excellent research
        credentials as well as extensive industry experience.The branch helps students to deal with the real life
        challenges in the field of Mechanical and Mechatronics industries and equip them with the fundamental concepts
        and techniques of mechatronics applications, relevant to emerging technological advancements.It also focusses
        on Computer Aided Manufacturing, Design Engineering, Automation, Robotics.</string>

    <string name="nature_of_work">The Scholars will be required to help the faculty of LNM IIT, Jaipur in setting up modern
        laboratories in analog and digital electronics, Communication, Computers and digital library and for helping in the
        conduct of classes and laboratories. </string>

    <string name="scholars_intro">LNM Scholars are second-tier of the academic backbone of the Institute, after the faculty.
        You participate in academic activities, alongside the faculty, and prepare yourself for a career upgrade through
        additional qualification.</string>

    <string name="eligibility">•B. Tech. in Electronics, Communication, Computers or equivalent.\n
•M. Tech in Electronics, Communication, Computers or equivalent.\n
•M. Sc. Physics with Applied Electronics.deepa</string>

    <string name="scholarshp">The Scholars will be provided an honorarium of Rs. 13,000 -18,000 per month. (Typically,
        hostel accommodation is provided to bachelors.) The revision of the LNM Scholar honorarium is under active
        consideration, and a decision is expected soon.When these scholars register for MS or PhD, their tuition is
        waived by the Institute.</string>

    <string name="opportunity">The Scholars are strongly encouraged to register for higher studies. Candidates with a B.Tech.
        or an M.Sc. degree may do M. S. (by Research) and MTech and those with an M.Tech. degree may work for Ph.D. while
        working as LNM Scholar.\</string>

</resources>
